Guide to the John Vliet Lindsay Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- New York City Mayoral Personal Papers, 1965-1973; Part II
  - Jay Kriegel (Assistant to the Mayor), 1966-1973; Series XVI
    - Police Issues
      - Narcotics, 1968-1971 (Box 371, Folder 558-559)
      - National Guard, 1968-1969 (Box 372, Folder 560)
      - National Guard training, 1969 (Box 372, Folder 561)
      - Non-lethal force, 1968 (Box 372, Folder 562)
      - Non-precinct consolidationq, 1967 (Box 372, Folder 563)
      - NYSIS, 1967-1968 (Box 372, Folder 564)
      - Operation neighborhood, 1970-1971 (Box 372, Folder 565)
      - Orders in general, 1966-1969 (Box 372, Folder 566)
      - Organized crime, 1968-1971 (Box 372, Folder 567)
      - Paperwork, 1967-1968 (Box 372, Folder 568)
      - Parades, 1967 (Box 372, Folder 569)
      - Police Benevolent Association, 1969-1970 (Box 372, Folder 570)
      - Parking, 1969 (Box 372, Folder 571)
      - Parks, 1970 (Box 372, Folder 572)
      - Personnel, 1966-1972 (Box 373, Folder 573-574)
      - Personnel civilianization, 1972 (Box 373, Folder 575)
      - Personnel, colleges, 1969-1970 (Box 373, Folder 576)
      - Personnel, Civilian Review Board, 1965-1966 (Box 373, Folder 577)
      - Personnel exams, 1969 (Box 373, Folder 578)
      - Personnel, minority recruitment, 1971 (Box 373, Folder 579)
      - Personnel, residency, 1971 (Box 373, Folder 580)
      - Petitions, 1966 (Box 373, Folder 581)
      - Planning, 1969-1971 (Box 373, Folder 582)
      - Police women, 1967-1968 (Box 373, Folder 583)
      - Pornography, 1969 (Box 373, Folder 584)
      - Post office, 1968-1969 (Box 373, Folder 585)
      - Precinct Community Council, 1965-1967 (Box 373, Folder 586)
      - Precinct receptionist program, 1968-1971 (Box 373, Folder 587)
      - Press releases, 1967-1968 (Box 373, Folder 588)
      - Productivity, 1971 (Box 373, Folder 589)
      - Rand study, 1968-1970 (Box 373, Folder 590)
      - Recidivism, 1966-1970 (Box 374, Folder 591)
      - Reorganization, 1966 (Box 374, Folder 592)
      - Rewards, 1965-1970 (Box 374, Folder 593)
      - Right wing, 1966 (Box 374, Folder 594)
      - Riot legislation, 1968 (Box 374, Folder 595)
      - Robbery, 1971 (Box 374, Folder 596)
      - Rochester, Police Advisory Board, 1964 (Box 374, Folder 597)
      - Rules and procedures, 1968 (Box 374, Folder 598)
      - Sabbath law, 1969-1970 (Box 374, Folder 599)
      - Salaries, undated (Box 374, Folder 600)
      - Sargeants salaries, 1969 (Box 374, Folder 601)
      - Schools, 1969 (Box 374, Folder 602)
      - Science and technology, 1965-1968 (Box 374, Folder 603)
      - Scooters, 1968-1969 (Box 374, Folder 604)
      - Spanish language project, 1967 (Box 374, Folder 605)
      - Speeches, 1964-1966 (Box 374, Folder 606)
      - Sprint, 1967-1970 (Box 374, Folder 607)
      - Stakeouts, 1967-1968 (Box 374, Folder 608)
      - Statements, Police Review Board, 1967-1968 (Box 374, Folder 609)
      - Storefronts, 1966 (Box 375, Folder 610)
      - Strike force, 1969 (Box 375, Folder 611)
      - Summons project, 1967-1969 (Box 375, Folder 612)
      - Supervision, 1969-1971 (Box 375, Folder 613)
      - Synagogues, 1968-1970 (Box 375, Folder 614)
      - Taxis, 1970 (Box 375, Folder 615)
      - Tenant patrols, undated (Box 375, Folder 616)
      - Times Square, 1972 (Box 375, Folder 617)
      - Towaway, 1970 (Box 375, Folder 618)
      - Traffic, 1966-1972 (Box 375, Folder 619)
      - Trainees, 1969-1970 (Box 375, Folder 620)
      - Training, 1968-1970 (Box 375, Folder 621)
      - Transcripts, Police Review Board, 1966 (Box 375, Folder 622-623)
      - Transit Authority, 1968-1970 (Box 375, Folder 624)
      - Uniform study, 1968-1970 (Box 376, Folder 625)
      - Veterans program, 1967 (Box 376, Folder 626)
      - Violent crimes, 1964, 1967-1968 (Box 376, Folder 627)
      - Walkie talkies, 1969-1970 (Box 376, Folder 628)
      - Wiretapping, 1968-1969 (Box 376, Folder 629)
      - Youth services, 1967-1969 (Box 376, Folder 630)
      - Communications
        - General, 1965-1970 (Box 377, Folder 631-632)
        - Call box system, 1967-1970 (Box 377, Folder 633-634)
        - Car locator system, 1967-1969 (Box 377, Folder 635)
        - Communication center, 1967-1968 (Box 377, Folder 636)
        - Emergency number, 1967-1970 (Box 377, Folder 637)
        - Emergency number 911, 1972-1973 (Box 377, Folder 638)
        - Fire department, 1967-1968 (Box 378, Folder 639)
        - Housing Authority, 1967 (Box 378, Folder 640)
        - Management survey, 1968-1969 (Box 378, Folder 641)
        - Radio frequencies, 1967-1968 (Box 378, Folder 642)
        - Sprint, 1969-1970 (Box 378, Folder 643)
        - Walkie talkies, 1969 (Box 378, Folder 644)
      - Crime
        - Control, federal, 1967-1970 (Box 379, Folder 645)
        - Control, state, 1967-1968 (Box 379, Folder 646)
        - Court rulings and legal rights of dependents, 1967-1969 (Box 379, Folder 647)
        - Insurance, 1971 (Box 379, Folder 648)
        - Justice, 1971 (Box 379, Folder 649)
        - Justice, bail, 1968 (Box 379, Folder 650)
        - Justice, 1967-1970 (Box 379, Folder 651)
        - Prevention, 1968-1972 (Box 379, Folder 652-653)
        - Prevention, citizen involvement, 1967-1969 (Box 379, Folder 654)
        - Prevention, citizens strike against crime, 1967-1968 (Box 379, Folder 655)
        - Prevention, community groups, 1968 (Box 379, Folder 656)
        - Prevention, Klapper trip, 1968 (Box 379, Folder 657)
        - Prevention, lighting, 1967-1968 (Box 379, Folder 658)
        - Prevention, mass media, 1968 (Box 379, Folder 659)
        - Prevention, schools, 1967-1968 (Box 379, Folder 660)
        - Reporting, 1967-1970 (Box 379, Folder 661-664)
      - Criminal Justice Coordinating Coounil (CJCC)
        - Auto theft, 1969 (Box 380, Folder 665)
        - Bail, 1969 (Box 380, Folder 666)
        - Block watch, 1969-1970 (Box 380, Folder 667)
        - Bowery project, 1968-1970 (Box 380, Folder 668)
        - Central pre-arraignment, undated (Box 380, Folder 669)
        - Clippings, 1969 (Box 380, Folder 670)
        - Community Institute, 1968 (Box 380, Folder 671)
        - Community patrol, 1968-1970 (Box 380, Folder 672)
        - Community probation, 1968 (Box 380, Folder 673)
        - Comprehensive plan, 1968-1970 (Box 380, Folder 674)
        - Correctional overcrowding, 1968-1970 (Box 380, Folder 675)
        - Correspondence, memoranda, 1967-1971 (Box 380, Folder 676-677)
        - Court delays, 1968-1970 (Box 381, Folder 678-679)
        - Court delays, Bronx project, 1968 (Box 381, Folder 680)
        - Court delays, pre-arraignment processing, 1969 (Box 381, Folder 681)
        - Court delays, traffic alert, 1967-1969 (Box 381, Folder 682)
        - Court delays, 24 hour arraignment, 1967 (Box 381, Folder 683)
        - Court employment, 1967-1969 (Box 381, Folder 684)
        - Crime prevention, 1967 (Box 381, Folder 685)
        - Information System, 1968-1969 (Box 381, Folder 686)
        - Information System, Judicial Data Center, 1969 (Box 381, Folder 687)
        - Information System, IBM report, 1968 (Box 381, Folder 688)
        - Information System, Simulmatics report, 1968 (Box 381, Folder 689)
        - Information System, Task Force report, 1968-1969 (Box 381, Folder 690)
        - Inquiry Board, 1969 (Box 382, Folder 691)
        - Legal interns, 1968-1970 (Box 382, Folder 692-693)
        - Long Island Railroad inquiry, 1969-1970 (Box 382, Folder 694)
        - Long Island Railroad report, 1969 (Box 382, Folder 695)
        - Material distributed, 1968-1969 (Box 382, Folder 696-697)
        - Material distributed, 1968 (Box 383, Folder 698)
        - Methadone, 1968-1969 (Box 383, Folder 699)
        - Minutes, 1969 (Box 383, Folder 700)
        - Model cities, 1970 (Box 383, Folder 701)
        - Model court, 1968 (Box 383, Folder 702)
        - Narcotics, 1967-1970 (Box 383, Folder 703)
        - Office of Criminal Justice, 1966-1968 (Box 383, Folder 704)
        - Operation Safe City, 1969 (Box 383, Folder 705)
        - Operation Safe City, 911, 1969 (Box 383, Folder 706)
        - Operation Safe City, auto theft, 1969 (Box 383, Folder 707)
        - Operation Safe City, burglary, 1968-1969 (Box 383, Folder 708-709)
        - Operation Safe City, groups, 1969 (Box 383, Folder 710)
        - Operation Safe City, lights on, 1969 (Box 383, Folder 711)
        - Other cities, 1969 (Box 383, Folder 712)
        - Police personnel, 1970 (Box 383, Folder 713)
        - Prostitution, 1968-1970 (Box 383, Folder 714)
        - Preventive detention, 1969 (Box 383, Folder 715)
        - Religious attacks, 1969 (Box 383, Folder 716)
        - Security devices, banks, 1969 (Box 383, Folder 717)
        - Security devices, churches, 1969 (Box 383, Folder 718)
        - Security devices, demonstration, 1969-1971 (Box 384, Folder 719)
        - Security devices, locks, 1969-1970 (Box 384, Folder 720)
        - Security devices, locksmiths, 1968-1969 (Box 384, Folder 721)
        - Security devices, Oakland, 1967-1968 (Box 384, Folder 722)
        - Security devices, survey, 1968-1969 (Box 384, Folder 723)
        - Security Institute, 1968-1969 (Box 384, Folder 724)
        - Security panel, 1967-1969 (Box 384, Folder 725)
        - State planning, 1969-1970 (Box 384, Folder 726)
        - Stevens committees, 1970 (Box 384, Folder 727)
        - Trail commissioners, 1970 (Box 384, Folder 728)
        - Trail delays, 1970 (Box 384, Folder 729)
        - Vera, 1965-1966 (Box 384, Folder 730)
        - Victims, 1967-1970 (Box 384, Folder 731)
        - Violent crimes, 1969 (Box 384, Folder 732)
        - Work release, 1968-1969 (Box 384, Folder 733)
        - Youth services, 1968-1970 (Box 384, Folder 734)
      - Planning Council
        - Air conditioned subways, 1968 (Box 385, Folder 735)
        - Capitol construction, 1969 (Box 385, Folder 736)
        - Computers, 1969 (Box 385, Folder 737)
        - Crime, 1969 (Box 385, Folder 738)
        - CUNY (City University of New York), 1970 (Box 385, Folder 739)
        - Kindergarten, pre-kindergarten, 1967 (Box 385, Folder 740)
        - Middle income housing, 1967-1968 (Box 385, Folder 741)
        - Midtown parking garage, 1967 (Box 385, Folder 742)
        - Miscellaneous, correspondence, 1969 (Box 385, Folder 743)
        - Navy yard, 1969 (Box 385, Folder 744)
        - Park maintenance, 1969 (Box 385, Folder 745)
        - Park projects, 1969 (Box 385, Folder 746)
        - Parking violations, 1969 (Box 385, Folder 747)
        - Policy Planning Council, refuse disposal, 1967-1968 (Box 385, Folder 748)
        - Project management, bus shelters, 1969 (Box 385, Folder 749)
        - Project management, rent control, 1968-1969 (Box 385, Folder 750)
        - Project management, safety surfacing, 1969 (Box 385, Folder 751)
        - Project management, taxi licensing, 1969 (Box 385, Folder 752)
        - Rents, 1968-1969 (Box 385, Folder 753)
        - Sanitation, 1969 (Box 386, Folder 754)
        - Sewers, 1969 (Box 386, Folder 755)
        - Third Water Tunnel, 1968 (Box 386, Folder 756)
        - Times Square Development Council, progress report. Mayor's Office of Apparel and Industry Planning and Development, 1972 (Box 386, Folder 757)
        - Water disposal, 1971 (Box 386, Folder 758)
        - Welfare, 1969 (Box 386, Folder 759)
  - Constantine Sidamon-Eristoff (Assistant to the Mayor), 1966; Series XVII
    - General Personnel Files 1966
      - Accountants (Box 387, Folder 1)
      - Administrative assistants (Box 387, Folder 2)
      - Architects, city planners (Box 387, Folder 3)
      - Arts, cultural (Box 387, Folder 4)
      - Attorneys (Box 387, Folder 5-6)
      - Clerks, senior, bookkeepers (Box 387, Folder 7)
      - Commerce, small business (Box 387, Folder 8)
      - Community relations and organizations (Box 387, Folder 9)
      - Computer technicians (Box 387, Folder 10)
      - Confidential, per Labor Department (Box 387, Folder 11)
      - Education (Box 387, Folder 12)
      - Electricians (Box 387, Folder 13)
      - Engineers (Box 387, Folder 14)
      - General departmental assistants (Box 387, Folder 15)
      - General management (Box 387, Folder 16)
      - General workers (Box 387, Folder 17)
      - Health; hospitals (Box 387, Folder 18)
      - Human rights (Box 387, Folder 19)
      - Inspectors and investigators (Box 387, Folder 20)
      - Insurance (Box 387, Folder 21)
      - Judicial (Box 387, Folder 22)
      - Men, staff résumés (Box 387, Folder 23)
      - Men, lower staff (Box 388, Folder 24)
      - Men, political (Box 388, Folder 25)
      - Public relations, women's résumés (Box 388, Folder 26)
      - Men, top talent (Box 388, Folder 27)
      - Miscellaneous, part time (Box 388, Folder 28)
      - Motor vehicle operators (Box 388, Folder 29)
      - Personnel management (Box 388, Folder 30)
      - Photography (Box 388, Folder 31)
      - Press releases (Box 388, Folder 32)
      - Résumés from Congressman Paul A. Fino (Box 388, Folder 33)
      - Puerto Rican correspondence (Box 388, Folder 34)
      - Real estate, housing (Box 388, Folder 35)
      - Résumés (Box 388, Folder 36)
      - Secretary (Box 388, Folder 37)
      - Women, top talent (Box 388, Folder 38)
  - Steven Isenberg (Assistant to the Mayor), 1970-1973; Series XVIII
    - 1970-1973 (Box 389, Folder 1-9)
  - Richard Weston (Assistant to the Mayor), 1972-1973; Series XIX
    Series XIX is sub-divided into three sections:
    Administration
    Advance and Scheduling
    Personnel Files
    - Administration, 1972-1973
      - General (Box 390, Folder 1-2)
      - Big Six Mayoral Conference (Box 390, Folder 3)
    - Advance and Scheduling, 1972-1973
      - Miscellaneous (Box 390, Folder 4)
      - Mayoral staff follow-up (Box 390, Folder 5)
      - Scheduling memoranda (Box 390, Folder 6-7)
      - Walking tours (Box 390, Folder 8)
      - Counties
        - Chautauqua (Box 390, Folder 9)
        - Dutchess (Box 390, Folder 10)
        - St. Lawrence (Box 390, Folder 11)
        - Saratoga (Box 390, Folder 12)
        - Schenectady (Box 390, Folder 13)
        - Schoharie (Box 390, Folder 14)
        - Schuyler (Box 390, Folder 15)
        - Seneca (Box 390, Folder 16)
        - Suffolk (Box 391, Folder 18)
        - Sullivan (Box 391, Folder 19)
        - Tioga (Box 391, Folder 20)
        - Tompkins (Box 391, Folder 21)
        - Ulster (Box 391, Folder 22)
        - Warren (Box 391, Folder 23)
        - Washington (Box 391, Folder 24)
        - Wayne (Box 391, Folder 25)
        - Wyomins (Box 391, Folder 26)
        - Yates (Box 391, Folder 27)
    - New York City, 1972
      - Cars (Box 392, Folder 28)
      - Estimate, Board of (Box 392, Folder 29)
      - General (Box 392, Folder 30)
    - Personnel, 1972-1973
      - Addiction services (Box 392, Folder 31)
      - City Planning Commission (Box 392, Folder 32)
      - Consumer Affairs, department of (Box 392, Folder 33)
      - Corrections (Box 392, Folder 34)
      - Correspondence, general
        - A-F (Box 392, Folder 35)
        - G-L (Box 392, Folder 36)
        - M-R (Box 392, Folder 37)
        - S-Z (Box 392, Folder 38)
      - Economic Development Association (Box 393, Folder 39)
      - Ed, task force (Box 393, Folder 40)
      - Emergency Employment Act (Box 393, Folder 41)
      - Environmental Protection Administration, vacant positions (Box 393, Folder 42-43)
      - Fire department (Box 393, Folder 44)
      - General (Box 393, Folder 45)
      - Hall of Science (Box 393, Folder 46)
      - Housing and Development Administration (Box 393, Folder 47)
      - Human Resources Administration (Box 393, Folder 48)
      - Job letters, 1972 Oct-Nov (Box 393, Folder 49)
      - Labor Relations, office of (Box 393, Folder 50)
      - Langsam, Janet (Box 393, Folder 51)
      - Mayoral (Box 393, Folder 52)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 393, Folder 53)
      - Neighborhood Action Prog am (Box 393, Folder 54)
      - Neighborhood Government, office of (Box 393, Folder 55)
      - New York City Housing Authority (Box 393, Folder 56)
      - Off-Track Betting (Box 393, Folder 57)
      - Police (Box 394, Folder 58)
      - Press (Box 394, Folder 59)
      - Public Events, department of (Box 394, Folder 60)
      - Transportation Administration (Box 394, Folder 61)
      - Water Supply, Board of (Box 394, Folder 62)
      - Youth Counsel Bureau (Box 394, Folder 63)
      - Youth Services Agency (Box 394, Folder 64)
  - Peter Goldmark (Assistant to the Mayor), 1965-1970; Series XX
    Series XX is sub-divided into two sections:
    Correspondence, 1969-1970
    - Chronological File 1969-1970
      - 1969 January 2-February 25, March 3-June 24, July 7-September 29, October 1-December 30 1969 January 2-February 25, March 3-June 24, July 7-September 29, October 1-December 30 (Box 395, Folder 1-9)
      - 1970 January 1-June 9 1970 January 1-June 9 (Box 396, Folder 10-11)
    - Research Subject Files
      - Air Pollution Implementation manuel, 1968 October 1 (Box 396, Folder 12)
      - American Indian issues, 1969 (Box 396, Folder 13)
      - Capital construction, 1969 (Box 396, Folder 14)
      - Center for Community Change, 1970 (Box 396, Folder 15)
      - Center for Community Change, boardmeeting, 1969 September 1 (Box 396, Folder 16)
      - Center for Community Change, boardmeeting, 1969 December 9 (Box 397, Folder 17)
      - Center for Community Change, information, 1969 (Box 397, Folder 18)
      - Choate School, the, 1970 (Box 397, Folder 19)
      - Citizens Advocate Center Report to Center for Community Change, 1970 February 24 (Box 397, Folder 20)
      - City of New York Executive Capital Budget, 1970-1971 (Box 397, Folder 21)
      - City Planning Commission, 1970 (Box 397, Folder 22)
      - City University of New York, state aid, 1969-1970 (Box 397, Folder 23)
      - Community revitalization, 1967, 1969 (Box 397, Folder 24)
      - Community school district plans, 1968-1970 (Box 397, Folder 25)
      - Crime rates, 1969 (Box 398, Folder 26)
      - Election statistics, 1960-1968 (Box 398, Folder 27)
      - Higher education, 1969 (Box 398, Folder 28-29)
      - Housing and Development Administration, 1965-1969 (Box 398, Folder 30)
      - Housing provisions of tax reform bill, 1969 (Box 398, Folder 31)
      - Independent Schools Summer Urban Education Project, the, 1969 (Box 398, Folder 32)
      - Inflation, 1969 (Box 398, Folder 33-34)
      - Narcotics research, 1969 (Box 398, Folder 35-36)
      - Neighborhood government, 1969-1971 (Box 399, Folder 37-38)
      - New York Civil Liberties Union, 1969 (Box 399, Folder 39)
      - Open enrollment, 1969-1970 (Box 399, Folder 40)
      - Polico, background information, 1969 (Box 399, Folder 41)
      - Public welfare policy programs, 1968-1969 (Box 399, Folder 42)
      - Rand-New York City Institute, 1968-1969 (Box 399, Folder 43)
      - Research statistics, 1969 (Box 399, Folder 44)
      - Tax reform and revenue sharing, 1969-1970 (Box 399, Folder 45)
      - Training Incentive Payments Program, 1969 (Box 400, Folder 46)
      - Transition Neighborhoods in New York City, 1969 December (Box 400, Folder 47)
      - Urban crisis and money, 1969-1970 (Box 400, Folder 48)
      - Welfare: public welfare policy programs, 1968-1969 (Box 400, Folder 49)
      - Welfare: overhaul of welfare system, 1969 (Box 400, Folder 50)
  - Photographs, 1950-1972; Series XXI
    Series XXI is sub-divided into seven sections:
    Pre-Congressional
    Congressional
    1965 Mayoral Campaign
    1969 Mayoral Campaign
    1972 Presidential Campaign
    Mayoral, General
    Sid Davidoff
    - Early Years, Pre-Congressional
      - 1949-1958 1949-1958 (Box 401, Folder 1)
    - Congressional Years 1965, n.d.
      - General (Box 401, Folder 2)
      - Portraits (Box 401, Folder 3)
      - Public officials (Box 401, Folder 4)
        See also: box 437
    - 1965 Mayoral Campaign
      - Volunteer photographers, list (Box 402, Folder 5)
      - Active campaigning (Box 402, Folder 6-8)
      - Active campaigning, contact sheet (Box 402, Folder 9)
      - Candid photographs (Box 402, Folder 10)
      - Celebrities (Box 402, Folder 11)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 402, Folder 12)
      - Official functions
        - Dinners and luncheons
          - General (Box 403, Folder 13)
          - Buffet Supper for Weekly Press, invitations, lists and photographs, 1965 September 29 (Box 403, Folder 14)
          - Luncheon for Foreign Language Press, invitations, lists, negatives, notes and photographs, 1965 October 7 (Box 403, Folder 15)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 403, Folder 16)
        - Openings (Box 403, Folder 17)
        - Presentations (Box 403, Folder 18)
      - Portraits, informal (Box 403, Folder 19-20)
      - Portraits, formal (Box 403, Folder 21-22)
      - Public officials (Box 403, Folder 23)
      - Sports (Box 403, Folder 24)
    - 1969 Mayoral Campaign
      - General (Box 403, Folder 25)
    - 1972 Presidential Campaign
      - General (Box 403, Folder 26)
    - General
      - Correspondence re: photographs, 1966-1973, undated (Box 404, Folder 27)
      - Candid photographs (Box 404, Folder 28)
      - Celebrities (Box 404, Folder 29-30)
      - Meetings and conferences (Box 404, Folder 31-32)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 404, Folder 33)
      - New York City sites (Box 404, Folder 34)
      - Official functions
        - Black tie affairs (Box 404, Folder 35)
        - Ceremonies (Box 404, Folder 36-37)
        - Ceremonies: The People Yes Festival, 1970 October 11-18 (Box 405, Folder 38)
        - Dinners and luncheons, informal (Box 405, Folder 39)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 405, Folder 40-41)
        - Openings (Box 405, Folder 42)
        - Presentations (Box 405, Folder 43-44)
        - Speeches (Box 405, Folder 45)
        - Swearing-in ceremonies (Box 405, Folder 46)
      - Portraits, formal (Box 405, Folder 47)
      - Press conferences and television appearances (Box 405, Folder 48)
      - Public officials
        - Domestic (Box 405, Folder 49)
        - International (Box 406, Folder 50)
      - Sports (Box 406, Folder 51)
      - Street scenes (Box 406, Folder 52-54)
      - Trips (Box 406, Folder 55)
      - Trips: visit to Yad-Vashem, Jerusalem, Israel, 1972 December 6 (Box 406, Folder 56)
    - Sid Davidoff
      - Correspondence re: photographs, 1966-1968, undated (Box 407, Folder 57)
      - Candid (Box 407, Folder 58)
      - Celebrities, correspondence and photographs (Box 407, Folder 59)
      - General functions
        - Black tie affairs (Box 407, Folder 60-61)
        - Campaign rally (Box 407, Folder 62)
        - Celebrations (Box 407, Folder 63)
        - Dinners and luncheons (Box 407, Folder 64)
        - Inaugural (Box 407, Folder 65)
        - Miscellaneous (Box 407, Folder 66)
        - Presentations (Box 407, Folder 67)
        - Speeches (Box 407, Folder 68)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 407, Folder 69)
      - Office scenes (Box 407, Folder 70)
      - Portraits, formal (Box 407, Folder 71)
      - Public officials, international (Box 407, Folder 72)
      - Sports (Box 407, Folder 73-74)
      - Street scenes (Box 407, Folder 75)
  - Audio Material, 1965-1972; Series XXII
    Conditions Governing Access
    Original audiovisual materials, as well as preservation and duplicating masters, may not be played. Researchers must consult use copies, or if none exist must pay for a use copy, which is retained by the repository. Researchers wishing to obtain an additional copy for their personal use should consult Copying Services information on the Manuscripts and Archives web site. Copies of commercially produced audiovisual materials contained in this collection cannot be made for researcher use outside of the repository.
    - 1965 Campaign Songs and Speeches